This application demonstrates the different aspects of software globalization:

- A single executable with world-wide functionality (fully Unicode enabled for Windows 2000 and Windows XP).

- Locale independency by using Windows NLS APIs to display data (dates, numbers, time, etc.) within a user's desired format.
To access the list of supported locales on line, visit:
http://www.microsoft.com/globaldev/nlsweb/


- Multilingual editing using standard edit controls.
To learn more about multilingual text support in Windows 2000 and Windows XP, check out:
http://www.microsoft.com/globaldev/articles/multilang.asp

- Multilingual input locales within edit control fields.

- Font selection and their affect on displayed data.

- Multilingual user interface and satellite DLLs
To learn more about multilingual user interface and how you can offer your own solution (for all platforms including Win9x), check out:
http://www.microsoft.com/globaldev/articles/muiapp.asp


To learn more about globalization, visit our globalization guidelines at:
http://www.microsoft.com/globaldev/wrguide/wrguide.asp